https://coreconnexion.de/en/data-privacy-notice/

Media
For GDPR please refer to the Datenschutzerklärung on www.coreconnexion.de
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for https://www.coreconnexion.com, https://www.coreconnexion.de. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
Eva Vigran, is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Eva Vigran only has access to/collect information that you voluntarily provide via email or other direct contact from you.
In order to use this website to enroll in programs organized by the Eva Vigran or my organizers or to contact Eva, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name, email address, and phone number). This information is used to promote and share information regarding educational work in my field, and to contact you about the products/services on my site in which you have expressed interest.
Right now there is no online shop. But when the online courses will be available you, you must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (such as PayPal account) to purchase goods and/or services from Eva Vigran.
This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. Eva Vigran does not and will not sell, rent, or share financial information with anyone. If I have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
Eva Vigran will not share your information with any third party outside of Core Connexion, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask me not to, I, may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from me at any time. You can safely unsubscribe from my newsletter at any time by clicking “unsubscribe” on the bottom of the emails.
You can also do the following at any time by contacting me via the email address given on the website:
See what data I have about you, if any. Change/correct any data I have about you. Have me delete any data we have about you. Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
I take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that I am not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at eva@coreconnexion.net.
To change your privacy setting, e.g. granting or withdrawing consent, click here:
Settings
Data protection
Details
Imprint
|
Privacy Policy
English
English
Deutsch
, Owner:
(Registered business address: Germany), processes personal data only to the extent strictly necessary for the operation of this website. All details in the privacy policy.
Data protection
Details
Imprint
|
Privacy Policy
English
English
Deutsch
, Owner:
(Registered business address: Germany), processes personal data only to the extent strictly necessary for the operation of this website. All details in the privacy policy.
Loading details
Back
Ok
Ok
